Guide to the Stan Healy Photographs and Papers 1890s-1990s (bulk 1940s-1970s)
Maureen and Mike Mansfield Library, The University of Montana--Missoula
- Accession 1990-016 Photographs, circa 1890s-1970s; Series I; 6.5 linear feet (2,700 images)
  - North Higgins Avenue, Stoverud Jewelry display window, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 1, Photo number 90-0537)
  - North Higgins Avenue, boat in front of Hotel Florence, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 1, Photo number 90-0538)
  - North Higgins Avenue, boat in front of Hotel Florence, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 1, Photo number 90-0539)
  - North Higgins Avenue, boat in front of Hotel Florence, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 1, Photo number 90-0540)
  - Campbell field, Christmas tree sale, Missoula, Montana, 1950 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0541)
  - Corner of Broadway and Orange, men talking, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 1, Photo number 90-0542)
  - Orange Street, wrecked car with police looking on, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 1, Photo number 90-0543)
  - Orange Street, wrecked car with police looking on, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0544)
  - Orange Street, wrecked car with police looking on, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0545)
  - Orange Street, wrecked car, police investigating, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0546)
  - American Legion, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0547)
  - Corner of Pine and Orange Streets, St. Francis Xavier Catholic Church, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0548)
  - Corner of Pine and Orange Streets, St. Francis Xavier Catholic Church, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0549)
  - Spruce Street, pet and costume parade, Missoula, Montana, July 10, 1956 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0550)
  - Spruce Street, pet and costume parade, Missoula, Montana, July 10, 1956 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0551)
  - Children lined up on Spruce Street for the pet and costume parade, Missoula, Montana, July 10, 1956 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0552A)
  - Pet and costume parade on Spruce Street, Missoula, Montana, July 10, 1956 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0552B)
  - Spruce Street, pet and costume parade, Missoula, Montana, July 10, 1956 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0553)
  - Spruce Street, pet and costume parade, Missoula, Montana, July 10, 1956 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0554)
  - Spruce Street, pet and costume parade, Missoula, Montana, July 10, 1956 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0555)
  - Spruce Street, truck in front of old jail, Missoula, Montana, 1950 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0556)
  - Spruce Street, truck in front of old jail, Missoula, Montana, 1950 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0557)
  - Spruce Street, school patrol, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0558)
  - Spruce Street, looking east, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0559)
  - Corner of Spruce and Alder Streets, looking east, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0560)
  - Stephens Avenue, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0561)
  - Southside street scenes, Missoula, Montana, circa 1950 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0562)
  - Southside street scenes, Missoula, Montana, circa 1950 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0563)
  - Southside street scenes, Missoula, Montana, circa 1950 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0564)
  - Southside street scenes, Missoula, Montana, circa 1950 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0565)
  - Southside street scenes, Missoula, Montana, circa 1950 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0566)
  - Higgins Avenue Legion parade, after J.C. Penney fire, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0567)
  - Higgins Avenue Legion parade, after J.C. Penney fire, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0568)
  - Higgins Avenue Legion parade, after J.C. Penney fire, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0569)
  - Higgins Avenue Legion parade, after J.C. Penney fire, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0570)
  - Higgins Avenue street scene, looking north, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0571)
  - Higgins Avenue Timberjack parade, movie premier, Missoula, Montana, 1955 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0572)
  - Higgins Avenue Timberjack parade, movie premier, Missoula, Montana, 1955 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0573)
  - Higgins Avenue Timberjack parade, movie premier, Missoula, Montana, 1955 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0574)
  - Higgins Avenue Timberjack parade, movie premier, Missoula, Montana, 1955 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0575)
  - Higgins Avenue Timberjack parade, movie premier, Missoula, Montana, 1955 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0576)
  - Higgins Avenue Timberjack parade, movie premier, Missoula, Montana, 1955 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0577)
  - Higgins Avenue Timberjack parade, movie premier, Missoula, Montana, 1955 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0578)
  - Higgins Avenue Timberjack parade, movie premier, Missoula, Montana, 1955 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0579)
  - Higgins Avenue Timberjack parade, movie premier, Missoula, Montana, 1955 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0580)
  - Higgins Avenue Timberjack parade, movie premier, Missoula, Montana, 1955 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0581)
  - Higgins Avenue new street lights turned on, Missoula, Montana, December 6, 1949 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0582)
  - Higgins Avenue new street lights turned on, Missoula, Montana, December 6, 1949 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0583)
  - Higgins Avenue new street lights turned on, Missoula, Montana, December 6, 1949 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0584)
  - Higgins Avenue new street lights turned on, Missoula, Montana, December 6, 1949 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0585)
  - Higgins Avenue new street lights turned on, Missoula, Montana, December 6, 1949 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0586)
  - Higgins Avenue street lights and vehicles at night taken from above, Missoula, Montana, December 6, 1949 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0587A)
  - Higgins Avenue new street lights turned on, Missoula, Montana, December 6, 1949 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0587B)
  - Higgins Avenue street lights and vehicles at night taken from above, Missoula, Montana, December 6, 1949 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0588A)
  - Higgins Avenue new street lights turned on, Missoula, Montana, December 6, 1949 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0588B)
  - Woody Street, scenes across from Missoula County Courthouse, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0589)
  - Woody Street, scenes across from Missoula County Courthouse, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0590)
  - Streetcar rails in the street, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0591)
  - Parked streetcars, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0592)
  - A wrecked Simons streetcar, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0593)
  - A wrecked Simons streetcar, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0594)
  - A streetcar repair unit, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0595)
  - Streetcars, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0596)
  - Streetcar, Daly Addition, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0597)
  - Streetcar, Daly Addition, boarded by passengers, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0598)
  - Streetcar, Daly Addition, North Higgins Avenue, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0599)
  - Streetcar, Daly Addition, repairs being made, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0600)
  - Streetcar, westside, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0601)
  - Streetcar, Daly Addition, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0602)
  - Streetcar, Daly Addition, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0603)
  - Streetcar, westside, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0604)
  - Streetcar, interior, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0605)
  - West Front Street Star Garage, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0606)
  - West Front Street Star Garage, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0607)
  - Wordens Market, car in foreground, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0608)
  - Wilma Theater, Missoula, Montana, September 7, 1955 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0609)
  - Wilma Theater, Missoula, Montana, September 7, 1955 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0610)
  - Wilma Theater, Missoula, Montana, September 7, 1955 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0611)
  - Lincoln Apartments, Ryman and West Spruce Streets, Missoula, Montana, 1950 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0612)
  - Western and Atlantic Hotels, Higgins Avenue, Missoula, Montana, October 3, 1955 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0613)
  - Stan Healy and Thunderbird, Western and Atlantic Hotels, Higgins Avenue, Missoula, Montana, October 3, 1955 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0614)
  - Priess Hotel, Shapard Hotel fire, Missoula, Montana, January 3, 1955 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0615)
  - Priess Hotel, Shapard Hotel fire, Missoula, Montana, January 3, 1955 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0616)
  - Old car (1908 Buick) in front of Belmont Hotel, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0617)
  - Old car (1908 Buick) in front of Shapard Hotel, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0618)
  - Old car (1908 Buick) in front of Shapard Hotel, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0619)
  - Street cleaning in front of Northern Hotel, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0620)
  - Street cleaning in front of Northern Hotel, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0621)
  - Street cleaning in front of Northern Hotel, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0622)
  - Street cleaning in front of Northern Hotel, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0623)
  - Belmont Hotel (Victoria) on North Higgins Avenue, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0624)
  - Parade on Higgins Avenue, Royal Neighbor float, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0625)
  - Parade on Higgins Avenue, Knights of Columbus float, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0626)
  - Parade on Higgins Avenue, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0627)
  - Installing traffic light in front of Palace Hotel, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0628)
  - Installing traffic light in front of Palace Hotel, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0629)
  - Installing traffic light in front of Palace Hotel, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0630)
  - Installing traffic light in front of Palace Hotel, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0631)
  - Belmont Hotel on North Higgins Avenue, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0632)
  - Belmont Hotel on North Higgins Avenue, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0633)
  - Belmont Hotel, Missoula, Montana, undated; Stan Healy's Thunderbird in foreground (Box 2, Photo number 90-0634)
  - Belmont Hotel on North Higgins Avenue, Missoula, Montana, 1950 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0635)
  - Lenox Hotel, on the corner of West Broadway and Woody, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0636A)
  - FBI Most Wanted List, Missoula Police Station (?), undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0636B)
  - Hotel Florence parking garage under construction, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0637)
  - Hotel Florence parking garage under construction, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0638)
  - Demolition of Gem Theater, West Front Street, Missoula, Montana, November 22, 1955 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0639)
  - Demolition of Gem Theater, West Front Street, Missoula, Montana, November 22, 1955 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0640)
  - Demolition of Gem Theater, West Front Street, Missoula, Montana, November 22, 1955 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0641)
  - Demolition of Gem Theater, West Front Street, Missoula, Montana, November 22, 1955 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0642)
  - Demolition of Gem Theater, West Front Street, Missoula, Montana, November 22, 1955 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0643)
  - Demolition of Gem Theater, West Front Street, Missoula, Montana, November 22, 1955 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0644)
  - Demolition of Gem Theater, West Front Street, Missoula, Montana, November 22, 1955 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0645)
  - Gem Theater on West Front Street Missoula, Montana, 1955 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0646)
  - Fox Theater, Orange and Main Streets, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0647)
  - Fox Theater, Orange and Main Streets, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0648)
  - Interior of Harnois Theater, East Main Street, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0649)
  - Interior of Harnois Theater, East Main Street, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0650)
  - Interior of Harnois Theater, East Main Street, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0651)
  - Interior of Harnois Theater, East Main Street, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0652)
  - Interior of Harnois Theater, East Main Street, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0653)
  - Interior of Harnois Theater, East Main Street, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0654)
  - Harnois Theater, East Main Street, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0655)
  - Harnois Theater after it became a Liberty Lanes bowling, East Main Street, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0656)
  - Roxy Theater, South Higgins Avenue, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0657)
  - Road construction on South Higgins Avenue, Missoula, Montana, 1949 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0658)
  - Roxy Theater, South Higgins Avenue, Missoula, Montana, 1949 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0659)
  - Road construction on South Higgins Avenue, Missoula, Montana, 1949 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0660)
  - Roxy Theater, South Higgins Avenue, Missoula, Montana, 1949 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0661)
  - Roxy Theater, South Higgins Avenue, Missoula, Montana, 1949 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0662)
  - Unidentified building, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0663)
  - Unidentified building, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0664)
  - Construction of Sentinel High School, South Avenue, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0665)
  - State Employment office on West Pine Street, Missoula, Montana, circa 1952 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0666)
  - State Employment office on West Pine Street, Missoula, Montana, circa 1952 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0667)
  - Telephone operators before dial system, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0668)
  - Check in desk at Missoula Hotel, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0669)
  - Alley behind Palace Hotel, Missoula, Montana, 1957 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0670)
  - Alley behind Palace Hotel, Missoula, Montana, 1957 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0671)
  - Pulling up bricks on North Higgins Avenue, Missoula, Montana, 1949 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0672)
  - Pulling up bricks on North Higgins Avenue, Missoula, Montana, 1949 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0673)
  - North Higgins Avenue after Shapard Hotel fire, Missoula, Montana, 1955 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0674)
  - Repaving North Higgins Avenue, Missoula, Montana, 1949 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0675)
  - Repaving North Higgins Avenue, Missoula, Montana, 1949 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0676)
  - Repaving North Higgins Avenue, Missoula, Montana, 1949 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0677)
  - Repaving North Higgins Avenue, Missoula, Montana, 1949 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0678)
  - Corner of North Higgins Avenue and Main Street, Missoula, Montana, 1952 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0679)
  - Corner of North Higgins Avenue and Main Street, Missoula, Montana, 1952 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0680)
  - Corner of North Higgins Avenue and Main Street, Missoula, Montana, 1952 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0681)
  - Corner of North Higgins Avenue and Main Street, Missoula, Montana, 1952 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0682)
  - Corner of North Higgins Avenue and Main Street, Missoula, Montana, 1952 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0683)
  - Corner of North Higgins Avenue and Main Street, Missoula, Montana, 1952 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0684)
  - Old cowpuncher at Murphy's Corner, Missoula, Montana, Summer 1951 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0685)
  - Old cowpuncher at Murphy's Corner, Missoula, Montana, Summer 1951 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0686)
  - Old cowpuncher, holding a Highlander Beer, stands by a parking meter with his horse at Murphy's Corner, Summer 1951 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0687A)
  - Old cowpuncher, holding a Highlander Beer, stands by a parking meter with his horse at Murphy's Corner, Summer 1951 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0687B)
  - Missoulian building, Missoula, Montana, October 3, 1955 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0688)
  - Murphy's Corner, Missoula, Montana, October 3, 1955 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0689)
  - Salvation Army drive against fast driving, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0690)
  - Interior Missoulian building, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0691)
  - Missoulian building, Missoula, Montana, September 1955 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0692)
  - Missoulian building, Missoula, Montana, September 1955 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0693)
  - Missoulian building on North Higgins, Missoula, Montana, September 1, 1955 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0693A)
  - Missoulian building on North Higgins, Missoula, Montana, September 1, 1955 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0693B)
  - Missoulian building, Missoula, Montana, September 1955 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0694)
  - Missoulian building, Missoula, Montana, September 1955 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0695)
  - Missoulian building, Missoula, Montana, September 1955 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0696)
  - Missoulian addition, Missoula, Montana, September 1955 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0697)
  - Missoulian addition, Missoula, Montana, September 1955 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0698)
  - Missoulian addition, Missoula, Montana, September 1955 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0699)
  - Missoulian addition, Missoula, Montana, October 5-6, 1955 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0700)
  - Missoulian addition, Missoula, Montana, October 5-6, 1955 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0701)
  - Missoulian addition, Missoula, Montana, October 5-6, 1955 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0702)
  - Missoulian addition, Missoula, Montana, October 5-6, 1955 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0703)
  - Missoulian addition, Missoula, Montana, October 5-6, 1955 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0704)
  - Missoulian addition, Missoula, Montana, October 5-6, 1955 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0705)
  - Missoulian addition, Missoula, Montana, October 5-6, 1955 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0706)
  - Missoulian addition, Missoula, Montana, October 5-6, 1955 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0707)
  - Missoulian addition, Missoula, Montana, October 5-6, 1955 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0708)
  - Missoulian addition, Missoula, Montana, October 5-6, 1955 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0709)
  - Missoulian addition, Missoula, Montana, October 14, 1955 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0710)
  - Missoulian addition, Missoula, Montana, October 14, 1955 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0711)
  - Missoulian addition, Missoula, Montana, October 14, 1955 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0712)
  - Missoulian addition, Missoula, Montana, October 14, 1955 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0713)
  - Missoulian addition, Missoula, Montana, October 14, 1955 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0714)
  - Missoulian addition, Missoula, Montana, October 14, 1955 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0715)
  - Missoulian, newsroom under construction, Missoula, Montana, September 29, 1956 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0716)
  - Post Office addition, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0717)
  - Post Office addition, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0718)
  - Loyola High School before the fire, Missoula, Montana, August 24, 1952 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0719)
  - Loyola High School before the fire, Missoula, Montana, August 24, 1952 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0720)
  - Loyola High School before the fire, Missoula, Montana, August 24, 1952 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0721)
  - St. Francis Xavier Catholic School and Church, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0722)
  - Missoula County High School, paving Higgins Avenue, Missoula, Montana, 1949 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0723)
  - Missoula County High School, paving Higgins Avenue, Missoula, Montana, 1949 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0724)
  - Fire engines at Missoula County High School, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0725)
  - Missoula County High School, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0726)
  - Missoula County High School, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0727)
  - Missoula County High School, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0728)
  - Old Roosevelt School, 901 6th Street West, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0729)
  - Tearing down old section of St. Patrick's Hospital, Missoula, Montana, circa 1955 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0730)
  - St. Patrick's Hospital, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0731)
  - St. Patrick's Hospital from afar, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0732)
  - Construction on St. Patrick's Hospital, Missoula, Montana, circa 1955 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0733)
  - Old section of St. Patrick's Hospital before being torn down, Missoula, Montana, circa 1955 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0734A)
  - Old section of St. Patrick's Hospital before being torn down, Missoula, Montana, circa 1955 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0734B)
  - St. Patrick's Hospital before demolition and reconstruction, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0735A)
  - St. Patrick's Hospital, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0735B)
  - Broadway Avenue, looking at St. Patrick's Hospital, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0736)
  - St. Patrick's Hospital before demolition and reconstruction, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0737A)
  - St. Patrick's Hospital before demolition and reconstruction, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0737B)
  - Old Northern Pacific Railway Hospital, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0738)
  - St. Patrick's Hospital, helicopter landing, Missoula, Montana, 1965 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0739)
  - St. Patrick's Hospital, helicopter landing, Missoula, Montana, 1965 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0740)
  - St. Patrick's Hospital, helicopter landing, Missoula, Montana, 1965 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0741)
  - Broadway Avenue, looking at St. Patrick's Hospital, Missoula, Montana, 1965 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0742)
  - St. Patrick's Hospital, helicopter landing, Missoula, Montana, 1965 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0743A)
  - Nurses at St. Patrick's Hospital going out with gurney to meet a helicopter landing on Broadway Avenue, 1965 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0743B)
  - Helicopter on Broadway Avenue which is being blocked off by a police officer and his patrol car at St. Patrick's Hospital, 1965 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0744A)
  - St. Patrick's Hospital, Missoula, Montana; helicopter on Broadway Avenue, a man is leaving the helicopter carrying a bag, 1965 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0744B)
  - St. Patrick's Hospital, helicopter landing, Missoula, Montana, 1965 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0745A)
  - St. Patrick's Hospital, Missoula, Montana, close up of the helicopter on Broadway Avenue, 1965 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0745B)
  - West Pine Street, houses before the fire station, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0746)
  - West Pine Street, houses torn down for fire station, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0747)
  - West Pine Street, houses torn down for fire station, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0748)
  - Higgins Avenue, Fire Prevention parade, Missoula, Montana, October 1967 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0749)
  - Higgins Avenue, Fire Prevention parade, Missoula, Montana, October 1967 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0750)